Hello!
We're standing in the parking lot of our cinema, Tinker Street Cinema, and as you can see, it's full tonight.
It's kind of a nice Saturday night.
It's cooling off.
It was a hot day, and everybody's coming to the movies tonight.
The people also park along the public highway, which is allowed.
It's pretty convenient for people to come, and it's very, very important to the town that we supply off street parking.
As you can see, today these murals, graffiti murals were done by artists who cam from New York City and it was promoted by the Varga Gallery, which is right next door to the cinema.
We sort of feed off each other.
It's like a cross thing where people stop and look and say wow.
It's quite a thing.
Ordinarily, it used to be a white wall, but look what they've done.
It's really incredible; it's beautiful.
These are the things that go on in small towns.
We try to exist.